

Mohamed Algarhy

Date of birth: 20/11/2001 | **Nationality:** Egyptian | **Gender** Male | (+20) 01128688235 |

mohamed6algarhy1@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohamed-adel-algarhy-9b0b181a5? lipi=urn%3Ali%3Apage%3Ad_flagship3_profile_view_base_contact_details%3BX3HtnffxSA2NwfLqZxHG9g%3D%3D

Minya, Egypt

About me: High-achieving college student with an aptitude for marketing, content creation, and graphic design. Experienced in building marketing strategies & creating designs through student activities. excited to discover more fields to gain more experience & skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

11/2019 - 12/2020

ORGANIZER - ENACTUS NEW BENI SUEF UNIVERSITY

12/2019 - 07/2020

GRAPHIC DESIGNER - CLICK WORKER WEBSITE

02/2020 - 09/2020

MEDIA MEMBER - OMA MARKETING

12/2020 - CURRENT

CONTENT CREATOR - GOOGLE DEVELOPER STUDENT CLUB - NAHDA UNIVERSIY

01/2021 - CURRENT

MARKETER - ENACTUS NEW BENI SUEF UNIVERSITY

03/2021 - CURRENT

CONTENT CREATOR - GOOGLE DEVELOPERS GROUPS - BENI SUEF

02/2021 - CURRENT

CONTENT CREATOR - SHWAR3NA COMPANY IN BENI SUEF

04/2021 - CURRENT

MEDIA COORDINATOR - FACE YOUR FEARS - FYF

04/2021

HUMAN RESOURCES - ACM ICPC - NAHDA UNIVERSITY

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

09/2019 - 07/2020

FACULTY OF LAW - ENGLISH SECTION - Beni Suef University

12/2016 - 05/2017

SPANISH LANGUAGE ONLINE COURSE - Duolingo Website

08/2017 - 01/2018

GERMAN LANGUAGE ONLINE COURSE - Duolingo Website

07/2019 - 11/2020 - Beni Suef

ENGLISH LANGUAGE - English City Academy

04/2020 - 06/2020

GRAPHIC DESIGN ONLINE COURSE - Russian Cultural center

12/2020 - 01/2021

SAS PROGRAMMING 1 - Artificial Intelligence Lab - Beni Suef University

04/2021 - 05/2021 - Beni Suef

GRAPHIC DESIGN - ADOBE PHOTOSHOP COURSE - Spot Co-Working Space

01/2021 - 01/2021

DIGITAL MARKETING ONLINE COURSE - Maharat mn Google

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): ARABIC

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C2	C2	C2	C2	C2
SPANISH	A1	A1	A1	A1	A1
GERMAN	A1	A1	A1	A1	A1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

PERSONAL SKILLS

Team-working skills | Presentation skills | Organizational and planning skills | Soft Skills | Critical thinking

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Microsoft Word | Microsoft Powerpoint | Research and analytical skills | Marketing skills (Digital Marketing, Pricing strategies, Marketing Mix, Product strategies) | Excellent knowlende of graphic software (Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Indesign, Adobe Illustrator)